Woke up in a pixel world
픽셀 세상에 눈을 떴어
Everything is squares and light
모든 게 네모와 빛뿐이야
Found a heart upon the ground
바닥에서 하트를 발견했어
Picked it up it felt so right
주웠는데 느낌이 너무 좋았어
Loading loading love dot exe
로딩 로딩 사랑.exe
Ready player two press start
레디 플레이어 투 스타트 버튼 눌러
Pixel love is all I need
내가 필요한 건 오직 픽셀 사랑뿐
Eight bit hearts on every screen
모든 화면 속 8비트 하트
Jump and dash and never stop
점프하고 대쉬하며 멈추지 않아
Level up until we reach the top
정상에 닿을 때까지 레벨 업
Side by side we fight the boss
나란히 보스와 싸워
Power ups along the way
가는 길엔 파워 업
Every coin I ever found
발견했던 모든 코인들이
Led me closer to today
오늘날 나를 더 가까이 이끌었지
Loading loading love dot exe
로딩 로딩 사랑.exe
Ready player two press start
레디 플레이어 투 스타트 버튼 눌러
Pixel love is all I need
내가 필요한 건 오직 픽셀 사랑뿐
Eight bit hearts on every screen
모든 화면 속 8비트 하트
Jump and dash and never stop
점프하고 대쉬하며 멈추지 않아
Level up until we reach the top
정상에 닿을 때까지 레벨 업
Pixel love is all I need
내가 필요한 건 오직 픽셀 사랑뿐
Eight bit hearts on every screen
모든 화면 속 8비트 하트
Jump and dash and never stop
점프하고 대쉬하며 멈추지 않아
Level up until we reach the top
정상에 닿을 때까지 레벨 업
Jump and dash and never stop
점프하고 대쉬하며 멈추지 않아
Level up until we reach the top
정상에 닿을 때까지 레벨 업